hello everyone this is E on E censored
Supernatural Bible changes on YouTube
and today we have our sister Rebecca
Rebecca I'm so glad you're here today
and I want to thank you for being the
very first person in a series of these
hourlong testimonies so thank you so
much for being here is raised um Mormon
LDS the it's called The Church of Jesus
Christ of latterday Saints and it's a
freemasonic branch off um false version
of Christianity but I did not know that
when you're raised in it you just know
what you know it was before the
internet uh I loved it I loved growing
up with the connections that I had in in
the Mormon Church um the service
projects that we did I was raised in a
great family where um there was music
and they everybody was sober so there
was no drinking or smoking or anything
like that it was happy was a two- parent
home lots of kids I was the last of like
a big family eight kids um the
surrounding people all my friends and
family were Mormon all my associations
at school was mostly Mormon
town uh I experienced my my my mom was a
really amazing mom like she didn't
gossip about people I never heard her
yell in my entire life she never raised
her voice she was so kind
so thoughtful and all of us were raised
everybody in my family has long-standing
marriages and healthy families and I
loved it I loved being I loved how
we could work together we could you know
the women would can vegetables together
do service projects for the
community um make blankets for the sick
kids at the hospital I mean it was full
of service projects full of biblical
types of Christianity out front for
people to experience and see but I
didn't know about the false doctrines I
didn't know I didn't realize how things
didn't line up um we memorized a lot of
scripture as kids growing up and then as
I got older in the high school I was
reading I read the Bible by myself
especially the New Testament and I I
loved it and so I just loved the whole
thing so I wanted to get married have 10
kids raised them all to be Mormon I was
all about it uh as I met my future
husband and we went to the temple and
back then the way that it operated was
Mormon temple is where you go to get
these endowments taken out where you
supposedly make covenants with God to
serve him for the rest of your life
and and that's where you get married
also like the next day after you take
your endowments or around the same time
you take these you you make these
covenants you also get married and so we
and all your friends and family that are
Mormon go with you who have Temple
recommends and only a top percentage of
Mormons have Temple recomend recommends
I think it's like 10% of the Mormons
have Temple recommend so these are all
like the big Believers the ones who are
really sincere
and so I went with all of them to the
temple and you have to do Temple
preparation
classes I'm sure because it was so such
a it's such an awful thing I'm sure it
had been very off-putting for a lot of
people so they started developing these
classes to prepare you where they tell
you it's all symbolic and not to take it
literally and that you know it's that
it's of God and and that you'll learn
more over time the more you go back and
all this stuff
and so I but you go blind as a kid you
aren't allowed to go into the temple um
it's it's something for people there's
there's different rooms in the temples
that Mormons have so there's a room
where like 12 year olds can go be
baptized for the dead which is a whole
other problem but and then there's rooms
where you go to get your endowments
taken out and then rooms where you get
married and then there's rooms that only
the top Elders of the church are allowed
to access and we don't even know what
goes on in those those places like it's
a secret we don't know they say it's
sacred not secret but whatever it's a
secret
and so I went to the temple um I
personally was horrified it's they've
changed the temple ceremony multiple
times since then they changed it in 1999
and then they changed it again in 2003
which supposedly they're supposed to
never change the temple that it was
perfect the way that Joseph Smith
outlined it
supposedly but uh it it it freaked me
out they've changed it mult multiple
times over the years because of the way
that it really upsets people uh when I
went we were taking death vows before we
even knew what we were promising that we
would have our throats slit and our
vowels split open if we ever spoke about
what happened in the temple uh and if we
ever broke our covenants and we didn't
even know what we were promising and I
found that very disturbing straight out
of the gate I found it just I found so
many things disturbing and very quickly
from the different conversations that
were being the different things they
were putting forward I recognized that
it was luciferian that it was that
Lucifer was the god of the Mormons and
this was came as a complete shock to me
because we were always told we were
Christian and that was drilled into us
that we are Christian and we serve
Christ and in the temple it didn't seem
to be obvious to the other people I
don't know how it wasn't obvious to
them maybe just from all the
brainwashing that we Christian Christian
Christian so it had didn't click in but
but I it was so obvious to me from so
many different things that were said and
done and the secret handshakes and the a
million problems that I saw during the
ceremony um that it was Lucifer who was
in charge and they even said his name in
the temple multiple times that that that
seemed to be who we were making these
handshakes with and I I was just so
horrified I was looking for an exit I I
couldn't find one because it's I not
famili I had never been to the temple
before and it was a room full of
curtains I didn't know where to go I
didn't know where to get out uh all my
friends and family were in there smiling
looking like it was the best thing ever
I but I was aware like this is a
horrible awful evil cult like I have got
to get out of this nightmare and I don't
know what it is and I don't know how to
get out and I kept thinking well they
warned us that this was just symbolic
they told us that this would
be you know that it not to take it
literally so I kept thinking well if I
just stick it out maybe by the end of
the ceremonies it will turn around and
it they'll explain how this is how
Christ came to set us free from all of
these sins of and connections to Lucifer
so I kept trying to stick it out hoping
that it would all turn around and that I
would be wrong because I
understood the magnitude of the loss
that would be involved if if if it
really was a from Lucifer so but we got
went through the whole ceremony took all
the vows went through the Witchcraft I
think it was white witchcraft they
didn't call it that but that's what it
was appeared to me to be and went
through to the other side and where all
my family welcomed me and I looked at
all of their faces knowing that I would
have to let leave them all let go of all
of them it was absolutely
heart-wrenching it it broke my heart and
I when we got out of the temple I was
basically yelling at everybody like you
lied to me you all lied to me how why
did you lie to me and you're not allowed
to discuss the temple outside of the
temple uh it's kept secret so they
didn't want me to they were more
concerned about me saying anything out
loud about it so my mom saidou know go
talk to your uncle he was the temple
president of the Salt Lake City Temple
like ask him your
questions you know it's okay we haven't
lied to you all this stuff so I I was
willing to because I was really hoping
that I was wrong I was really hoping
that I was seeing things
incorrectly so I went to go meet with
him very soon after like the next
day and we shared back and forth and it
I was he was saying we you know we just
have we don't all understand it we just
have to trust God and and I was like who
is your god I Lucifer is your god like
what what you know and he we
communicated about what happened and
what it meant what the symbols
meant and I realized that what I was
saying was surprising him that he'd
never thought about it the way that I
said the way I saw things and I was like
well tell me I'm wrong like give me an
alternative view how do you view it like
how do you make this Christian because I
don't see a way for this to be
Christian and he was just sort of
stunned he was like he didn't have an
answer he didn't have a way to EXP
explain it in a Christian way he was
like I just never thought about it like
that I'm like well how did you think of
it like what what is this and he's like
I I don't know we're just supposed to
take these covenants on faith and I'm
thinking this is a man who's been in the
church all of his life he's been in
higher up callings and he has no idea
what this means like what do you what
anyway it just was very obvious to me
that of what it was and I can't and I
think it's because I had read the Bible
by myself so sincerely I think that it
stood out as being hypocritical and
contradictory um but when I left and I I
began to sort of do a slow fade from the
church after that I never went back to
the temple I stopped going to church you
know went less often but I was newly
married I mean that's part of what traps
you is like I had married a Mormon man
who wanted a Mormon wife and a Mormon
family and the day you get married it
was like the day that I found out
that my whole religion was a lie so I
think that that traps you um and peer
pressure at a certain point they're
hoping that you have enough invested
that you won't be willing to lose it and
question it and that you're too
brainwashed by that point to even be
able to think clearly um but I just
couldn't swallow that I had been raised
my family was a great family I'd been
raised in such a beautiful home that I
knew the importance of motherhood and
and I knew the importance of of like I
wanted my do like my children to have
truth and I became pregnant it was an
accidental surprise pregnancy soon after
that
um and I just kept thinking I I don't
know what to teach my children I don't
even know what's true and because I'd
been taught that it was that we were
Christians I thought that meant that all
of Christianity was a hypocrisy and all
of Christianity was a lie it bothered me
that the front was saying we love Jesus
and then the back in the back end it's
Lucifer so I thought maybe all of
Christianity was like that that the bad
guy is the good guy and all this
confusion was there so I was so deeply
confused I do remember that before my
daughter was born I remember saying a
prayer and um I think I was with my
husband at the time but I just I was
saying I God I now I don't even know who
you are I don't know if you're real I
don't know what the truth is but if
you're real I don't want to go to hell I
don't want to do wrong
things but I know now that I've been
part of a lie and I don't know how big
the LIE is I don't know where the truth
is I don't know what to teach my
daughter and I want my daughter to have
truth and I have no idea what it is um
you know and so I asked for protection I
said I'm going to have to kind of go out
in the big bad world and try on all the
things because I've been taught that if
you leave the church you're apostate and
it's all darkness and it's all bad
things and and so I was terrified but I
I I was I just couldn't
handled that living a lie for the rest
of my life was not an option for me
and so slowly I began I tried to consult
with my husband along the way um to ask
him how he felt or what we could try or
where we could look for truth and I mean
bless him he was so kind to me he was
such a good hearted such a kind-hearted
man so sweet to me and but he he was
like well our families wouldn't have
lied to us you know like like he didn't
know what to make of it but he just
thought well I'm just going to trust
that there's something here and I'm
going to kind of just stick with
Mormonism uh he was very patient with me
because he knew I was upset and that I'm
kind of all or nothing and I wanted I
wanted the truth so he put up with me
while I ended up bringing so much evil
into our home because I didn't I didn't
know where the truth was so I
started going out um like to different
things like I if I would hear about a
group Gathering I went to like women's
drum circles or their their Gatherings
of they would gather around the
Moonlight and dance in the Moonlight and
I'd be like okay maybe this is something
and then like that no and I would there
was a lady there that was a psychic and
I was like well maybe this is something
well nope and I was basically doing
experiments I mean of just trying to
figure out like try something on for a
while like a new hat and then see if it
fit or see if I could figure out what
the truth was and understand it mentally
or logically and if it didn't fit I
would go to the next thing and it was a
series of like a decade of just at least
a decade of just the next thing and the
next thing I mean I went to different
Christian churches around um and they
were dead as a doornail the pastor was
the only one doing any work the people
were passive when I would ask them who
is Jesus to you like what did Jesus do
for you or what do you do for Jesus or
what what's your testimony there it was
nothing it was there was no passion
there was I couldn't I mean it was dead
dead churches and they acted like it was
just a social club they didn't act like
they even believed it and I wasn't
seeing the power of God manifest in
their lives in anything I mean I was
like well hey the Christians had more to
offer than this they were involved in
service projects and and you know the
counterfeit light of Christianity of
false Christianity had more light than
what I was Finding in Christian churches
and so I was like well this isn't it
either so I kind of at that point
crossed Christianity off the list
completely and moved I mean not
completely completely because I had a
soft spot I loved the New Testament I
had a soft spot for Jesus but I I just
kind of kept searching I went to
Unitarian churches I went to oh my my
gosh if I it's like searching in my mind
I went I I bought a book on religions I
started studying all different world
religions
Buddhism I went to
um I mean it was just one thing after
another I was talking to everybody that
I could asking them what they based
their life on and I'd always been taught
Mormons are very very strict about
Following the Leader you don't have
independent thought you don't know they
don't teach you how to think critically
or
independently so when you step out of
something like that you're so blank
you're so so naive you're so like dumb I
mean for lack of I mean just I'm not
insulting the Mormons they're very
intelligent people there's many doctors
and lawyers and like really smart people
among them but you're just trained to
follow the leader like and that is
dangerous to think on your own so I just
was walking around clueless clueless and
um I what I noticed caught my attention
which I think catches a lot of people's
attention when they're younger
especially is that that groups that had
passion where they were at least like if
they had no Truth at least they were
passionate for whatever it was they were
into I felt like there was something
there there was a false um like if they
operated in the Supernatural that was
something that touched me because I
think that I'd always God had always
operated in me somewhat supernaturally
throughout my life from the time I was
born and it might have been because of
curses on my family if I had witches in
my family background and stuff and so
maybe I had some like psychic tenden or
something because of the Witchcraft and
the gener generational curses and the
Demonic that was following in my family
line but IID had Supernatural
experiences I'd seen Beyond the Veil I
had seen beings on the other side and
things like that and so when when I
would go to places that had no
connection at all with the supernatural
of on any level it would strike me as
just materialistic as completely dead
and I knew there was power and there was
something on the other side so when
groups were accessing that in some way I
didn't have any discernment to have the
distinction between good spiritual good
spiritual access and wicked spiritual
access and like demonic spirits versus
the Holy Spirit I didn't have any
understanding of that at all
so I met um a group that was teaching
supposed Christian meditation that's how
they advertised it they sent me a
pamphlet
and I was and I thought oh wonderful
wonderful and they were so sounded great
to me so I went to learn this meditation
and it initially gave me spiritual highs
that were Supernatural and and direct
access to Supernatural so I was like oh
good this is something alive something
powerful something real so I was very
interested in that and um I pursued I
pursued it heavily um and my daughter
was also very sick she had um diabetes
she was the youngest diabetic ever
diagnosed in her State and we were going
through a lot as a family with those
trials uh because of the money involved
the debts that were involved with with
the hospital visits it would be $20,000
every time we had to put her in the
hospital and there
were it was out it were outrageous
things beyond our ability to pay and a
lot of stress with trying to get her to
be stabilized she was too young to tell
us like how she felt so we were
constantly having to give her blood
Pricks and blood checks and it was
before some of the more modern
technology of like censor that can check
your blood sugar all the time
and um they have ways of keeping tabs on
it that aren't quite as invasive all the
time but back then it was blood checks
and so we had to prick her finger you
know 10 times a day to try to find out
where she was at and she couldn't tell
us if she felt strange so she would pass
out from a coma being too low or she
would go too high or she would have
seizures or she we were constantly in
and out of the hospital trying to help
her get stabilized trying different
kinds of insulin and stuff so all this
was going on in the background and I was
under an enormous amount of stress and
pressure and I wanted so much to have
something to offer my daughter and I
knew I didn't I was aware that I was
empty and devoid of anything to teach
her so it was this it was something that
it was almost like I was on warp speed
looking for the truth because I was
trying to find out what to bring my
daughter and so I mean I was the most
open-minded person to the point that my
brains were falling out I was so open
minded it it would would blow people's
minds if they realized how open-minded I
was I mean probably every demon in every
demon out there was Finding their way
into my life at that time uh because I
had an Open Door invitation I was
completely like is it this is it that is
it this is it that um and even things
that the Mormon church had taught me
were wicked and evil I was open to them
because I was like well the Mormon
church is lying so maybe they're lying
about this too so I put everything as a
question mark and I thought well I
remembered the scripture about like if
you do the doctrine or something like if
you will know the doctrine if you do it
I'm not saying the scripture correctly
but uh it was something any man know
does the doctrine they will know of it
or something like that and so I was kind
of thinking well I'll figure it out by
doing these things and finding out what
the fruit is or what the result is of
these things so taking basically I was
learning the hard way basically I tried
to cross off things that were going to
be obvious bad things like I I'd already
heard of enough people that have been on
like heroin or something that had their
lives fall apart that I was like okay
that's definitely off the list I don't
need to try heroin you know but I was
pretty much everything else was an open
possibility in my life at that time so
um I'm trying to think what else I mean
there were so many things that I was
investigating this finally this group I
think the one of the last groups was
this meditation group this Christian
supposedly Christian meditation group um
and it I think I was most pulled towards
it because of the dedication of the
people they were were giving up their
lives they were selling their
possessions they were they were coming
together they were teaching around the
world and I thought well they mean they
mean business and they're dedicated and
so
um there was there was a lot involved
during this time so it kind of mish
mashes together but I was involved in a
car accident that caused a partial
Amnesia and I could remember words I
could remember all the basic things in
life but I couldn't remember or the
order of anything during that time so I
was hospitalized for 3 months the
doctors all said you're going to be
disabled for life you had there's no
hope of recovery for you um you
are you know we'll sign the papers for
you to get disability because it's it's
sort of a hopeless situation and what
they meant by that was that like I
couldn't I couldn't remember how to take
a shower for example I would remember
the word shower I would remember what it
was but when I would go to try to take a
shower I would have to
I couldn't remember the order of
anything so I'd be like is it is it
towel first and then conditioner and
then water and then shampoo or is it I I
couldn't get the order of anything right
even walking I was like I had to relearn
how to walk like is it tow heel to heel
no heel toe heel toe okay and so I
started to have to have people make
lists for me um a detailed lists of like
how to do everything and I had to follow
the list or I could get confused and
lost and forget and couldn't keep the
order of anything on my own at all in my
head
um during there was there was so much
happening during that time also right
about that time it was right around that
I I'm not sure exact the exact order but
I also ended up opening enough demonic
doors that I had the experience of
becoming fully possessed for a period of
time um and what that was like I was
standing with my husband um we were in I
was in my bathroom and it was like
almost like a lightning bolt struck my
hand and came into my body and I started
I fell down and it sort of shook me and
I I knew something was horribly wrong I
had felt something enter my body that
shouldn't be there and it was very
powerful and I uh fell down and my
husband was like are you okay are you
okay I was like I don't know I don't
know something's wrong and my cat came
in the room and the cat was coming up to
nuzzle next to me and then it looked
into my eyes and the second the cat
looked into my eyes eyes it arched its
back it it did a hissing you know Yow
and ran like as fast as it could away
from me and eventually when I made it to
a mirror I could see the demon in the
mirror inside of my body I could see it
it was ugly and horrific and it was
terrifying and um it started to take
over so it would push my personality
down and it would manifest where I would
be unconscious to what it was doing so I
became violent um and my husband took me
you know he was a big big strong guy so
he held me tight and like kept me from
being violent and took me into the
hospital and was like do another CAT
scan like the like the the car accident
must have damaged more of her brain than
we thought like something's wrong she's
being really violent and then I would
sort of like calm down and come to and
they would check me with CAT scans they
couldn't find anything so they're like
no take her home she's fine she's just
damaged from the accident but she's okay
and my husband was worried because I had
we had a daughter A young daughter
daughter in our home and I would keep
breaking out in this violence and and go
unconscious and pass out and so he was
like okay something's really really
really wrong here and when I would be
present my spiritual eyes were open in a
in the sense of kind of like your third
eye like something that shouldn't be
open it was my eyes were open in a way
that God doesn't want your spiritual
eyes opened I could see demons
everywhere I saw I didn't know they were
demons though so I didn't know what I
was seeing because some of them look
like animals and they look like
different things like I wasn't I they
were just terrifying so we would walk
like when he I need to ask you a
question I need to ask you a question
I'm listening to you share so you use
the word like Supernatural and
spiritual and it can be a little
confusing
so this is before you knew Jesus so can
you kind of elaborate what you mean by
that before you were a
Christian uh yes um I I think yeah I
mean it it's it can be kind of hard to
explain but like I always saw things
that other people didn't see and um
right but I mean because there there's a
supernatural that can be satanic and
then there's a supernatural that can be
um Heavenly like a miracle yes um
spiritual can be you know demonic and it
can be um Christ focused Christ induced
you know so during this time do you
think that you were just seeing demonic
entities having demonic
experiences yes I wasn't connected to
the Holy Spirit guiding me through these
things it was completely being open to
spiritual and Supernatural on the
Demonic side of things but I didn't know
that because I didn't know at the time I
didn't know there was a Vision I didn't
even know I hadn't been taught I didn't
have a vocabulary for the for the things
that I was experiencing or seeing like
Mormons will lightly brush across the
topic of like demons or this spiritual
Supernatural but they don't really go
into depth they don't really believe in
Hell per se there's a lot of things that
they don't believe in biblically that
are or that they brush over and brush
past and Joseph Smith had a lot of
Talking to Angels that were delivering
other doctrines that were anti- the
Gospel of Jesus Christ so the
supernatural was an Open Door within
Mormonism by the virtue of its founder
Joseph Smith who was a con artist in my
opinion a liar and somebody who saw the
supernatural but in the through
Freemasonry open doors of demons and
things like that de demonic inspiration
demonic influences okay he and something
that yeah and something that he did that
was it's one of the most dangerous
things is that he mixed true
Christianity with false Christianity and
with the lies of Satan and so it becomes
very difficult to tell the difference
when you're raised in something that is
mixed like that because it all gets
mashed together so you you kind of pick
up that there's truth somewhere you're
like there's something amazing here and
you hold to that and you love that and
you can't just you aren't able to
separate your in Clarity your thoughts
about what
is what is the wicked part and what is
the righteous part it's all mish mash
together so when you grow
up right but the fundamental difference
would be that there are many fundamental
differences but a big one is that they
do not believe that Jesus is God they
believe he's Lucifer's brother and that
their God comes from the planet
cab yes and that God is a spirit they
don't teach yeah and they don't teach
that God is a spirit they teach that God
has a flesh and Bone body and that we
can become that he's raising us like
literal spiritual children that someday
we'll become
gods of our own just like raising a
family and then we'll have spiritual
children of our own and they'll become
gods and like it's it's it's an attempt
to become a God and I believe that the
angel morona was actually Lucifer
appearing to exactly was appearing to
Joseph Smith deceiving him and teaching
him to te to teach false lies to the
people and it opens doors like M of my
one of my um ancestors was burned as a
witch in Salem when we did our family
history so there was also witchcraft in
the family line and that brings
generational curses of sin on the family
line so I think I was born with demons
and that will mislead you as well
because you are getting all this mixed
influence like I'm reading the Bible on
one hand which is this great influence
and memorizing scripture which is this
great influence and then having all
these mixed things that and when you're
born in with demons in in your family
and in your
life uh you're confused from the get-go
you're automatic Bally starting off like
with a handicap of confusion in your
mind so yeah it was all demonic
confusion I do feel like there was
always some thread of connection to
Jesus that I felt in my heart throughout
and I feel like because of the prayers
that I prayed sincerely where I was
truly asking for guidance and for truth
I do think he kept me from falling off
the ledges like I was getting into all
kinds of evil opening all kinds of evil
doors but he knew that I was trying to
find and figure out what the truth was
and I feel like he sort of kept me
pulled me back from the edges where I
probably would have I probably wouldn't
be here I would probably be dead or in
hell at this point already for sure if
kept an eye on me I want to go ahead and
just touch upon this really quickly
since you come from Mormonism but I know
that Mormons wear their sacred underwear
and were you also required to wear your
sacred underwear with Masonic symbols on
it yes and we aren't taught what the
symbols mean everything's about taking
it on faith but yeah I put when I
remember that when I from the moment I
put them on I felt suffocated I remember
feeling like hatred for them and I was
surprised by that because I was taught
we were supposed that we there were such
a great protection in the spiritual
world and they were supposed to help us
and I felt like I had to claw them off
my body I felt enraged having them on my
body they upset me so much and I felt
confused by that as well because I'd
always been taught to be modest to cover
up and so I was like wearing modest
clothing continuing to kind of try to
figure out how to fit this Mormon thing
into my life but it felt awful at a
certain point I took them off but it
wasn't until I was completely done with
Mormonism like completely Unwound from
that but then after I Mormonism it's
like where do you go after that what age
are you required to start wearing
them when you get your endowments in the
temple so when you get B they changed
now they've changed some policies so
some girls are getting endowed and going
on missions when they're 18 and that's
when they would start wearing them and
then but back then you got your
endowments out when you got married so
you start wearing them when you're
married and you wear them 20
247 yes you could hypothetically take
them off to take a bath and stuff like
that but people some people are very
strict about it like they'll have them
hanging off their toe while they take a
bath and then like they never take them
off how do they I I have to ask you this
question how do they think that the
their sacred underwear these garments
with Masonic symbols protect
them they have an interesting thing
because when Joseph Smith was was split
off from the Freemasons he began to
teach the church members not to join
Freemasonry because he stole their
ceremonies he stole not all of them but
he stole some of their ceremonies so he
wanted to keep Mormons from ever joining
with the Freemasons who are also they're
a Christian fronting service group but
behind the scenes they are also
luciferian so the Mormons know there's a
connection between Freemasonry and
Mormonism but they don't know they don't
know much about it they don't they've
been just taught that Luc they've been
taught that Lucifer is the lightbringer
and that somehow that's good because
he's Jesus's brother and that even
though he's got like brought the bad
idea forward of like dark things that
he's still somehow maybe he's the
lightbringer in some way so they don't
see it as black and white the way that
true Christians go oh Lucifer is the
enemy period he is a creation of God and
wicked and he's fallen they don't see it
that way so they don't they get confused
by so when Lucifer's mentioned in the
temple they don't necessarily see that
as a giant flaming red flag I did I I
felt it in my spirit I I was like this
is so wrong how is the bad guy the good
guy in here in the temple like
something's terribly terribly wrong um
but I
think that happens and then so I I'm
sorry I interrupted you but you were
talking about you were talking about
your exposure to these demonic what you
at the time you thought were supernal
but in retrospect you realize there were
demonic activity so I'm going to let you
go ahead and continue from that that
point
um supposed to yeah yeah and like they
are definitely when I say Supernatural
too like unhuman levels of strength for
example while I was possessed when I
would pass out I have very many
witnesses of this this wasn't just also
in my head my husband was uh working for
the fire department at the time and he
was friends with the all the policemen
and uh when I he started reaching out to
them for help so when I became violent
he was having trouble containing me and
so he would he had his police officer
friends come and I would wake up with
like a police officer on every arm and
leg and then I would pass out again and
I would hear stories when I woke up
about how I'd thrown them against a wall
from them like laying like kneeling on
my limbs which it should be impossible
from a person laying down to have that
kind of Supernatural strength to throw
grown men off their body and throw them
at a wall but I did and it wasn't me it
was and the the demon was claiming
itself to be Legion which later
obviously that's pretty obvious from the
Bible and a lot of demons claim to be
Legion that aren't but I pretty sure it
was something like that where I I had
Supernatural strength I was uh being
given tours of like I didn't know it was
hell back then but I think that it was I
was being given tours of these horrific
places while I was unconscious in the
body while my body was freaking out and
being driven by demons doing these crazy
things I was um being given tours
essentially of by these ugly looking
creatures I didn't know they were demons
I didn't know what I was seeing but they
were giving me chours of these horrific
places like the dungeons dark dark
Wilderness fiery ugly nasty stuff
torture chambers and they were show they
were torturing beings and they were
picking them up like P puppets and
moving them like puppets and making them
fight with each other and stuff and they
were telling me S join with us serve us
and so this won't happen to you if you
do not we will torture you the way that
we're showing you that we're doing this
to others we will torture you forever
they were telling me that I would be
reincarnated Life After Life After Life
and that they would torture me every
life if I didn't uh work with them and
help them and join with them and serve
them and I was horrified and I was just
like absolutely not and I started uh I
started in the spirit realm you know um
I was kind of free floating in the
spirit realm and I was it was like a
near-death experience it was so I
started um you know asking for help and
I started asking if if Buddha is there
to help me help me if Jesus is there to
help me help me like I don't know I
don't I didn't know what was going on I
was so baffled and so confused at that
point and I did receive help and I was a
bit confused about who was helping me
because even the light being that came
to get me I I wasn't even sure who it
was because I'd been taught so many
confusing things so I was just uh this
light being brought brought me to show
me a glimpse of of great of great light
and then I was sent back to my body um
so I woke up and after I after that it's
like the demon C Cal down or something I
don't know if the big one left and I
just was left with other demons or if
the big one calmed down they' been
Mormons had been praying over me and
anointing me but it wasn't working
because Satan can't cast out Satan and
uh psychics my all the friends that I'd
gathered all these Wicked people were
were trying to help me because my
husband was calling everybody trying to
get help for me so psychics had been
trying to get these demon to calm down
and go away they couldn't do it I had
all kinds of people trying to work on me
and they couldn't get it taken care of
but after I had in the spirit Realm been
rescued by this light being who I think
was Jesus now but back then I didn't
know um it seemed like that that big
demon that had completely possessed me
either went away or was repressed or
something it was it calmed down so at
that point you know everybody there had
been Witnesses I had spit on my mother I
had my mom had been trying to get help
my mom had called for help and like this
demon had been doing all kinds of just
awful things and so I there were a lot
of witnesses to this period of time and
I they would haul they would they
started hauling me to mental
institutions to because they couldn't
but even they couldn't they couldn't
contain me they didn't know what to do
with me so um when I woke up I was
actually I'm trying to remember which
time because I I for me it was all kind
of Jumpy because I would pass out have
visions wake up in a new environment
pass out wake up in a new environment so
it was kind of spotty so sometimes I
woke up in the hospital sometimes I woke
up with my family sometimes I woke up I
was all kind of over the all over the
place uh I woke up
um um I think at some point I woke up at
home I don't remember all the processes
of getting there but at some point oh no
no I woke up in the mental hospital
first and I was being held in the state
facility and
uh that's a whole other story that could
be for another time I guess but like I
was there for a period of time where I
didn't think I would ever get out I was
like okay I'm never going to have a job
never going to have a life like when i'
I'm recorded as being an insane person
everybody's witnessed apparently me
acting crazy because I was hearing
stories from the people that visited me
in the hospital they were telling me the
things that had happened and I was just
like oh my gosh like I'm insane or
something's and I didn't know what had
happened to me
really so um and I didn't even dare I
don't think any of us uttered the word
demon back then because I think it was
like a forbidden word but I would see
demons on people and attached to people
and stuff and I but I didn't know what
they were so I was just scared and
baffled and Confused beyond belief um
but I started trying my best I was like
okay it's like I felt like I was a
runaway train that had like was crashing
down a mountain at rapid speed and it
didn't look like it was going to end up
in a good place so I remember trying to
do my best to sort of put one foot in
front of the other and be like I'm going
to try to flush these medicines the
doctors are giving me out of my body
drink lots of water I'm going to try to
exercise I'm going to try to get my
right mind back and I I didn't I wasn't
approaching it from the place of
approaching Jesus because I didn't know
if Jesus was the answer right so I was
just kind of trying to use my best
guesses to improve my strength and move
forward um I did have a picture of Jesus
with me in the hospital and I do
remember saying prayers um and but not
really still really no idea what's going
on when I got out um I couldn't take
care of my daughter in the way that I
had i' lo my memory was off based I
couldn't couldn't like I couldn't even
water my plants or properly do my
laundry or shower I was like a mess and
my poor husband was trying to take care
of my daughter who was sick and now me
who'd been in an accident who was sick
and who'd been freaking possessed and
been causing trauma at home so I
everything was kind of calm after that
and then they let me out of the hospital
and it was calm and they just said
you're going to have to take your
medicine for the rest of your life and
you're going to have to be on disability
and like yes you've got these memory
problems and it's just how it is so I
said okay well you know I'm going to go
join
uh I'm going to go join while I'm
recovering I'm going to go join with
this Christian meditation group and go
stay with them because I'd met them
before and I had done some of their
meditation and I thought it was from
connected to Jesus so I didn't think
that was a problem so I was like okay I
told we talked to my husband I was like
okay you go get remarried because I am
not well and I've brought nothing but
bad things into our home and so I'm
going to I'm going to go and I'll try to
get healed but they're telling me I'm
never going to get healed so you get
remarried and then whenever I can get
better enough I'll come back and I'll
help be a team to help raise our
daughter and and so we talked about it
my mom was like we told my mom about her
plan and she was like this is a terrible
plan you guys are best friends and you
love each other so much like this is a
terrible idea but we were like well what
other idea we have we're broke we're up
to debt up to our eyeballs in debt with
different hospital bills we didn't know
what to do and we were just like
desperate and I was like he needs help
and it would that's the only kind thing
I could possibly do is go and let him
move on because he wants to be married
with to a Mormon and have a Mormon
family so that would be the only
gracious thing so I left I went to go
stay with the monks my husband got
remarried within six months um we did
phone calls with my daughter and stuff
she was about four or five at the time I
went to this group it was in
Oregon and we did yoga every day it was
Christian Yoga you know wink wink uh we
did yoga every day we did meditation
every day
we worked for the business there and it
did help my neurotransmitters reconnect
as far as just um being helped through
the process like if I would have just
gone and gotten a regular job I would
have gotten fired because I would forget
everything but these monks were very
patient with me that they would let me
write down lists of everything like like
I was a waitress and so I had to write
down like fill water bottles and fill
salt shaker I had to write everything
down and then I would just follow the
list and they were very very patient
with me and my memory issues and if I
asked them for help or told that I was
feeling overwhelmed they would they
would help me so it was a time of
healing for probably about a year maybe
a little under a year I was with them
healing and you know during that time
the whole divorce had happened my
husband had been remarried all that
stuff um let's see next big step so
anyway I continued down that path for
years longer I I went back and spent
time with my daughter and stuff but I
continued to stay in touch with this
Christian meditation group and I
continued to work with them for a long
time eventually I started to see the
fruits of that group I started to see
where it was leading people I saw the
arrogance I saw the form of godliness
but denying the power thereof I saw that
they had great Supernatural powers that
would come from the Demonic forces but
they didn't use them to praise God they
didn't use it to grow closer to God they
used it to Glory themselves and I
recognized that as an evil thing I
recognized that there that it was
something was terribly wrong and I
recognized that because they had they
were sort of Lawless it was like they
were sort of using the ideas of follow
the spirit but it like they weren't
identifying which spirit and they would
call things the holy spirit that weren't
that were leading people to be being
promiscuous they were supposed to be
celibate monks but they were there was
promis promiscuity happening and they
were sort of Lawless they could kind of
do anything and then and I started to
recognized that it led not to more
freedom but to bondage and I saw that
bondage taking hold more and more and
that was a moment when I started to
reconsider and I backed away from that
group and I had been involved with a lot
of different things but that that was a
moment when I started to reflect and
then in time was passing where I was
still just kind of like well if it's not
that what is it like what is the truth
what direction do I go and I'd so I'd
already given up everything to be a part
of that group when i' left my family and
my home to be with those Christian bunks
but now I was alone again and I had been
a massage therapist for a long time um
and I'd started to see problems with
that I I'd been under a lot of healers
I'd gone to because I was I knew that
something had been wrong because
a lot of the people I went to they said
that those things that had been demonic
they were saying well that's that was
just negative energy that was negative
thoughts or that was because of your
former religion or that's because of
religious Traditions it's just
dark-minded thinking so we're GNA he
cleanse you and heal you and so I went
to different shamanic healings I went
through different different massage
therapists that were healers and all I
went through every type of like healing
you can imagine and they were starting
to tell me you're totally cleared off
you're enlightened you're you're free
you're you're healed you're cleansed
you're so POS positive I was like a
beacon of positivity everywhere I went I
was like people would be like oh your
skin is glowing because I literally my
skin was literally like the crystals of
my skin were glowing because I took
really good care of my health back then
and stuff and so I was like oh I'm on
the right path I guess you know but I
didn't know exactly where to go next and
then um around 201
16 in the summer of
2016 I
saw the Mandela effects beginning to
unfold my daughter and I were together I
was Raising her at that time she was
living with me and I saw the um we both
saw her map change on her wall it was a
marer map it was on her wall we
recognized over that overnight the the
map had completely changed from what we
remembered the day before and we started
screaming we were kind of she jumped off
her bed and we she ran and hugged me and
we were like what in the heck is going
on there's just something weird that
that something stable and physical in
the material world could shift like
overnight it which seemed very
Supernatural to us and we were just just
like what is this if this can happen
like anything could happen so I ran to
get online looked online and saw that um
and saw that there were these Mandela
effects supposedly happening where
things were changing logos were changing
different things were changing and I was
just kind of glued to my screen trying
to figure out what all was changing and
what was happening and why and how and I
was very stressed and then I saw a
reference somebody said that the Bible
was changing and I was like what that
one hit me like T but that one hit me
more than anything even though I'd been
screaming about the map changing this
what this upset me so much to consider
so I immediately went and I found cat's
video thank thank God that that sister
cat here at e started showing videos
about this but she showed that the lon
in the lamb uh scripture had changed and
other scriptures and I knew what it was
as I'd read the Bible I knew what it was
supposed to say and I started to go on a
major research thing I started looking
grabbing I had tons tons of Bibles and
different I had Buddhist books and I
mean Zen books and Hindu books I mean I
had all kinds of like books of all over
the world but I had Bibles and I had my
old Bible that I had learned on
originally and I started pulling out all
the Bibles and was like oh my gosh and
as it started to hit I cried for weeks I
sobbed and sobbed and sobbed I mean it
was like uncontrollable tears my
daughter was like what is going on you
know because she'd seen the map changes
too and I was like honey the Bibles
changed and I never read her the Bible
I'd never encouraged her to learn these
things because I was still busy looking
for the truth to bring her and so I just
misled her I had taught her how to do
yoga and all kinds of stuff but I hadn't
she didn't know scripture so she didn't
know it had changed and I was like I
started to realize that Satan wouldn't
change something to the opposite meaning
if it had already been changed if it was
already a tool for control of the people
and the masses if it was already cor
completely corrupted he wouldn't have a
reason to change it and when it was
changed from like Lion to Wolf things
like that I would recognize that it had
changed from Something Beautiful to
something ugly ly and it was the moment
that it dawned on me the Bible had been
true and that that was the truth I'd
been looking for all this time when I'd
wandered around looking that it had been
I'd had it the whole time and it struck
me so hard I mean the grief and the
repentance and the horror and the shock
and I remembered the scriptures like
Amos 811 and 12 that had talked about
how there would come a time that there
would be a famine in the land for the
hearing of the word of the Lord and
stuff and so I recognized oh yeah
yes this is it this is the Bible
prophesied this this is this was
predicted and the fact that it had
punishments listed for people for
changing the Bible if they added to or
took away from the word what punishments
would be there for them and I was like
well of course there wouldn't have been
punishments listed if it couldn't be
changed if it was inherent if it
couldn't be and people wouldn't have
risked their lives trying to preserve
the Scrolls in Generations PRI prior if
Satan had been unable to to touch it to
come near it or to to attack it in some
way so it became kind of obvious to me
and I started to research more and
realized the Bible was like a
code that God had given us because in
Hebrew each letter is a number and that
these codes were something that Satan
had figured out how to access and change
the coding that CH that when they change
something in the Bible it changes
something in our material world and that
that's why these changes in the material
world were happening and that there was
a time that Satan would be given all
power to be able to do these things so
I I I just I was sobbing thinking about
what if what about all the people who
are going to turn to the Bible for truth
and they're going to get they're now
going to be
taught where the places where now Satan
is basically pretending to be Christ in
the Bible and taking away the goodness
and Glory of Christ and taking away the
cross and things like that and I
realized back then it was I don't know
if the cross had been tampered with back
then but they were tampering with so
many things it started to dawn on me
like the damage that this would do and
the way this would deceive potentially
Christians into following the Antichrist
and it it struck me so hard that I I
that was the moment I was like I was
wrong like I should have been a
Christian and I I need to be a Christian
so I was changing then but I wasn't born
again then so that was summer 2016 200
so I study kept studying the Bible I
talked to my family about it I I didn't
even tell them what was going on I just
asked them if they could tell me what
Isaiah 11:6 said and they can they could
quote it my sister quoted it directly
without even looking it up and I was
like well look it up it's not there and
she went to look and it her face turned
pale and my mom was there and my other
brother and like my had family there and
you know her face just went pale my
mom's face went pale and they were just
shocked and they looked at me for like
the answer and I was like I don't have
the answer I don't know why this is
happening I don't know what what's going
on but scripture is
changing and after that though they
never really wanted to talk about it I
think it was overwhelming to them they
didn't feel maybe smart enough to
understand what was happening and they
just stuck with what they knew and they
just didn't want to discuss it anymore
but during that whole year there had
been a whole transition process so then
in
2017 I was I was potentially looking to
be M uh married to a man who was
Christian he said he wouldn't marry me
unless I was Christian I was like I'm
Christian he's like no you're definitely
not Christian I was like yes I am he's
like no you're definitely not um he's
like I'm gonna take you to my pastor so
we took a drive to his Pastor uh was
Russian didn't speak much
English who definitely had the power of
God moving through him and through his
group for sure it was very powerful but
I I didn't know so what I I was very um
I was just coming from my head and my
heart of wanting to do the right thing
but I had didn't have the Holy Spirit
and didn't have an understanding of
really what it was to be a Christian so
he we we started fasting and the next
day he the pastor took me into his um
office and started asking me about my
sins and I didn't think I had sinned
because I didn't for some reason even
though I'd read the Bible I didn't
really understand sin I was like oh God
is all Grace all mercy and we just learn
as we go whoopsy dupsy if we you know
screw up we just learn from that and I
didn't have any kind of um contrite
heart about Sin in my life at all and he
had to explain it to me so he would he
had a list of things to check off like
have you done this and this and this
like these sins and I would check them
off and he was like and I confess them
basically and then he would have me read
a scripture that told us
what how you're not supposed to do that
thing and what kinds of consequences
come from that thing and in that moment
I started to realize like oh if I would
have listened to the Bible if I would
have taken it seriously and not done the
things it said not to do and done the
things it said to do I wouldn't have
hurt myself and others I wouldn't have
opened all of these doors I wouldn't
have caused so much suffering and I
would have brought my daughter truth and
in that moment it it's like conviction
hit and I was so sorrowful and and so
aware I had never truly been sorrowful
I've been sorry sorry I hadn't
recognized the Bible before but I hadn't
had sorrow for sin I didn't even
understand Justice and sin at all really
and he made it clear to me and I just
was so humbled and and aware of how
wrong I had been and then we were still
fasting so this went on for like nine
hours and then he he said he was going
to cast out demons and I was thinking
okay that's great sure go ahead and try
but I didn't think I had any because I'd
had all these healers from around the
world work on me and they all said I was
free and clear and they hadn't found
anything and it was all positive energy
so I was like okay sure do your healing
or whatever I'm all for it but I didn't
really think you would find anything and
then he began to pray and oh my gosh my
whole body crumpled over I I was so sick
and I could feel I could hear the demons
I could hear them screaming in my head I
could feel them leaving I could also see
in the spirit world I could see them
being pulled out I could see them
leaving and I was shocked by that I was
like what in the world what in the world
like I I didn't even know those were
there and it was this huge deliverance
and afterwards he put his hand above my
stomach and it started gurgling and
bubbling and I was like oh is this some
other demon or what is this and he
starts pulling his hand up like without
touching me or anything but just like
pulls his hand up my body and then he
says okay speak speak and I'm like I
didn't know what I was supposed to speak
so I didn't know what he was talking
about and he's like speak and I started
speaking and it was I was just to my
mind I was just babbling and he was like
yes yes glory to God the the you know
the holy spirit is coming you're
speaking in tongues and I was like what
because I'd been taught in Mormonism
that speaking in tongues was just Mormon
missionaries learning a new language to
go teach the gospel I didn't know
anything about speaking in tongues and I
was so surprised by this and so but it
was all happening without him telling me
what to do or what it was it was
happening without my you know mental
awareness of of of what was happening
exactly I mean I was choosing to open my
mouth to speak but I wasn't I didn't
mentally understand understand what was
happening and then we prayed and we
started to praise God and thank God we
went and joined everybody else in prayer
and just praising and thanking him and
this Holy Spirit was filling me I was
baptized the next day in the river and
it changed like my whole life for
example instantly what changed things
that had been with me my whole life
demons for example I'd always had
Suicidal Thoughts my whole life but I
didn't think they were Suicidal Thoughts
they because I didn't follow those
thoughts so I wouldn't have told anybody
oh I'm so sad I'm so suicidal I would
just have thoughts like I'm going to go
get bread today and I've got to go
shopping to get peanut butter and I
should maybe I could jump off the bridge
uh and I need to go get um you know some
some salad dressing or something and it
would be part of my daily thoughts to
commit suicide in a million different
ways all the time and it had been there
my whole life so I didn't think anything
about it I thought everybody had
thoughts like that I thought you were
suicidal if you said if you meant it if
you're really going to do something
about it uh and in the moment that after
that he had cast the demons out this
that left I didn't hear that voice at
all
I just feel like there's been so many
changes and so much growth and I'd made
lots of changes prior to that my life
had been pretty much like shifting 180
degrees over and over all these
different from one religion to another
religion to what but this was totally
different this was like oh I finally
found what I was looking for nobody else
in my family is is a born- again
Christian it truth is worth everything
truth is worth everything I would do it
again and I went through so much and oh
also and I also I've mentioned on your
show before cat that like God ended up
paying my bills and providing me with
with an abundant you know job and career
for a long time before I ever became
fully born again chrishna but he he paid
off my he paid off my debts he brought
abundance into my life because I think
he knew I was searching for the truth
and he took care of me and he still is
taking care of me in ways unexpected
ways all the time and um so my testimony
is that Jesus is it and truth is worth
everything even if you lose everything
and everyone and the only right way to
access the spiritual world is through
Christ and the Holy Spirit alone no all
other options are demonic portals are
demonic are demonic they are wicked they
are they lead to death and they are un
unallowed like they're not authorized by
Christ as ways to access the spirit
world they are unauthorized they are
Wicked Ways and but I think the thing is
in Born Again Christians the
Supernatural is moving but the holy
spirit is answering prayers performing
Miracles but it is it provides good
fruit people are living in ways that are
pleasing to the Lord they live free in
righteousness they cast sin away from
them they're peculiar from the world
they're separate from the world it's a
different it's a totally different thing
and the results are completely different
the Holy Spirit leads you to
righteousness it leads you to prune out
and cut away all the things that offend
him things that will hurt yourself or
others and things that are damaging in
your life it makes you do the work of
stepping up and stepping forward it's to
it's a totally different thing and you
get no glory and all glory goes to God
and all and and we you give him you give
him the credit for those powers that
come through and those insights and
those abilities but true
Christianity it's like it's not boring
it's not dead it's not and it is
Supernatural but it is moving
in righteousness it's moving in love
it's moving with the fruits of the
spirit love the holy spirit is like a
wind that blows through that keeps you
fresh and Alive keeps the water from
becoming stagnant and it's a beautiful
thing and I'm thankful I'm so thankful
to God the Bible changes we part of what
brought me to Christ and humbling me and
I really thought the whole church that
masses of people right after that would
have been pouring out of the churches
sobbing wailing crying repenting asking
God for forgiveness recognizing it's a
judgment on the church recognizing their
need for God but instead of that
happening the pride has kept people
blinded their unwillingness to love the
truth has kept them in darkness and they
don't they don't see care when we point
it out they still don't care but we're
hoping I'm hoping that there will still
be many more that will become willing to
see and that will seek the Living God
because the Holy Spirit leads us into
all truth and even without the Bible we
can still have the spirit guide us every
day and help us but is harder without
scripture to guide us to make sure we're
not off the path to make sure we're
following within his guidelines and but
we have to stay very close to him or
we're going to be led off the path when
we don't have scripture to refer to
anymore I was like it's Jesus Jesus is
everything and he set me free from
demons that had been B binding me my
whole life and it's still a process say
I'm still getting cleaned out I mean the
other day also praise report cat the
other day when you guys prayed for me um
the doctors had told me that I was going
to go blind my left eye um if I didn't
use their prescription eye drops and
that even if I did use their eye drops I
would probably go blind and you guys
praying for me my swelling went down my
eyes stopped being red I haven't used
the drops um because I don't want to use
phakia and sorcery to heal and just
trusting God and it I was scared though
I was kind of scared taking their eye
drops or I would go blind
and praise God praise God the blessings
of the saints come forward with healing
that is beyond what
doctors can can help us
with than than all of the healers of the
world the shamans and all of those you
know false
healers he he could find the evil that
was there that was hiding from them he
could find and dig out and overpower all
the powers of the enemy all the powers
that come from the Dark Side of of
spirituality and anybody who's following
the dark side in any way shape or form
give it up Let it Go and recognize that
truly Jesus overpowers them all he is
the Victor over all of that and his he's
not only the right way he is the Victor
he is the he is the winner that brings
has all good things and all good gifts
for his children and that he can help us
when no one else can when doctors can't
the doctors gave up on me which all the
way by the way I had a career a whole
career after they told me I would have
to be on disability I never went on
disability I had a whole career after
that and he financially set me free from
things the world couldn't set me free
from and from these false healers and
stuff so like every single thing that
the world tells you to trust in was
taken away from me and God can overcome
all of those things every single one of
those things and I just want to
acknowledge that that's what I was
that's what that whole trail of
information was to say is that truly
Jesus is everything and our provider and
our protector and our the one who knows
all and sees all God bless all those
people around the world that truly are
moving the gifts of the Spirit whether
they're with this group or not it
doesn't matter that those who truly love
Jesus we are united in spirit with them
and I'm thankful for them so Rebecca you
mentioned about the church and the fact
that the church has become cold and and
basically they become um apathetic and
Powerless and I think part of that is
that they're being led by wolves and
they're being taught false Doctrine now
that the scriptures have been perverted
satanically supernaturally and they're
now teaching the perversions as truth
there is a um a lack of power and
authority that's happening in the church
and we know that that Jesus always
warned us that there would be many false
teachers and this is what we're seeing
happen today and this is why it's
important that we seek Jesus Christ with
our whole heart mind soul and strength
God thank you so much for today and
hearing your testimony just brings me
great joy and Delight that you are now a
daughter of the king and truly
surrendered and submitted to him and I
know you love him and thank you for
being a sister in the Lord and um also a
friend and so I praise God for you and I
pray God's blessing over you in Jesus
name oh thank you amen and if I can be
saved anybody can be like I was so lost
I was so lost and so uh corrupted and so
if you know I don't want anybody to feel
tooo far gone I know there are PE there
are times when God will give somebody
over to a rep probate mind it can go too
far but you know it you have to be you
have to be really off base and and
really turn your back on God in a very
real and direct way for him to ever
leave you behind he's willing to come
for those lost sheep and I was very very
lost I'm so thankful to God for finding
me and rescuing me and he loves people
so much I was so wrong and so in error
but yet he loved me enough to come and
fetch me out and I'm so thankful for
that so he truly loves everybody and I
appreciate what you did for God in in
telling people about the Bible changes
because it brought me from Darkness to
light praise the Lord all right Rebecca
I'm gonna I'm goingon to close this up
and it's been great learning more about
you Rebecca thanks for sharing God bless